George S. McGovern Papers Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1957-1984 (bulk 1968-1972 )
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1957-1984; 105.42 linear feet 110 boxes Approximately 1,785 items
  - Subseries 5C, 1970-1984 February 22; 30.4 linear feet 32 boxes
    - 1973-1979, 1973-1984 February 22; 156 boxes
      - Theodore White with Alan Douglas, 1973 August 9; 601; 1 box (Box 827)
      - 1973 August 11, 569; 1 box (Box 827)
      - CBS TV and Cambodia Spots, 1973 August 15; 580; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Face The Nation, 1973 August 19; 609; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Theodore White Book Beat amd White-Paar, 1973 August 20; 600; 1 box (Box 827)
      - McGovern NBCTV Interview, 1973 August 22; 1670; 1 box (Box 827)
      - McGovern/Eagleton Author, Dick Dougherty, 1973 September 6; 176; 1 box (Box 827)
      - Democratic Telethon, 1973 September 15; 1174; 1 box (Box 828)
      - McGovern TV Capsules, 1973 September 18-19; 1175; 1 box (Box 828)
      - WMCA Radio, Dougherty, 1973 September 23; 875; 1 box (Box 828)
      - Dougherty/McGovern, Today, 1973 September 24; 175; 1 box (Box 828)
      - Watergate and Civil Liberties, ACLU, Michigan, 1973 October 14; 1135; 1 box (Box 828)
      - McGovern 4 R, 1973 October 19; 54; 3/4-inch 1 box (Box 828)
      - Today, 1973 November 7; 364; 1 box (Box 828)
      - 1974 Campaign spot #1-New Era of Hope, 2-inch portion of 1 box (Box 828)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 17, 1761.
      - 1974 Campaign spot #2-Inflation, 5 minutes 10 seconds 2-inch (Box 828)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 27, 1762.
      - 1974 Campaign spot #3-Special Interests, 1763; 2-inch 1 box (Box 828)
      - 1974 Campaign spot #4-Agriculture, 1764; 2-inch 1 box (Box 828)
      - 1974 Campaign Spot, 28; 2-inch 1 box (Box 829)
      - Great Lakes, 1974; 80; 16mm 1 box (Box 829)
      - 1974, 82; 16mm 1 box (Box 829)
      - McGovern Donors and Check Stubs, 1974; 675; 1 box (Box 829)
      - No. 326 Senator McGovern, 4 Cuts, 1974 February 22; 20; 2-inch 1 box (Box 830)
      - D.C. Press Conference, Social Security, 1974 March 21; 1523; 1 box (Box 831)
      - McGovern Radio News, 1974 March 22; 1540; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Fred Harris News Conference, 1974 March 25; 1537; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Wind, 1974 March 27; 1534; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Michigan and New Jersey Primaries, 1974 March 28; 1529; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Jennings CPI, 1974 March 28; 1530; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Tape 16, 1974 March 28; 1531; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Farm Issues, 1974 March 28; 1532; 1 box (Box 831)
      - George McGovern, President George, 1974 March 29; 1547; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Tape 25, 1974 April 2; 1528; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Cleveland, Ohio: McGovern-Kennedy Rally, 1974 April 2; 1543; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Wisonsin Primary, 1974 April 2; 1550; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Maryland Primary, 1974 April 2; 1551; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Columbus Press Conference/Dinner Speech, 1974 April 2; 1552; 1 box (Box 831)
      - LA Clergy Breakfast, California Primary, 1974 April 2; 1553; 1 box (Box 831)
      - 1974 April 2, 1560; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Democrats, 1974 April 4; 556; 1 box (Box 831)
      - State Treasury Charles Smith Fundraiser, 1974 April 28; 1330; 1 box (Box 831)
      - HHH Huron, 1974 May 25; 579; 1 box (Box 831)
      - HHH Huron Demo, 1974 May 25; 583; 1 box (Box 831)
      - McGovern, 1974 June 1-August 31; 544; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Today, Women Voters, 1974 June 13; 1522; 1 box (Box 831)
      - 1974 June 19, 1470; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Leo-Goldwater/Rockefeller Quote, 1974 July 8; 568; 1 box (Box 831)
      - McGovern Spots, 1974 August 1; 582; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Actualities, 1974 August 9-19; 1130; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Actualities, 1974 August 19-21; 1128; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Actualities, 1974 August 23-30; 1129; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Actualities and Eleanor at Woonsocket, 1974 September 1; 1127; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Mrs. McGovern on the Mike Douglas Show, 1974 September 3; 1324; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Frank Wallner Dinner, 1974 September 4; 1126; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Actualities, 1974 September 7-14; 1125; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Eleanor McGovern on Today, 1974 September 11; 1325; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Eleanor McGovern/Pia, 1974 September 12; 1338; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Eleanor McGovern, ABC TV, 1974 September 13; 1327; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Eleanor McGovern on Sunday, NBC TV, 1974 September 15; 1326; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Economic Briefing, 1974 September 15; 1541; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Actualities, 1974 September 15-October 2; 1124; 1 box (Box 831)
      - Spot #3: Special Interests, 1974 September 17; 37; 2-inch 1 box (Box 831)
      - Spot #4: Agriculture, 1974 September 24; 23; 5 minutes 2-inch (Box 831)
      - Actualities, 1974 October 2-5; 1122; 1 box (Box 832)
      - AP Phone Interview, 1974 October 3; 596; 1 box (Box 832)
      - Actualities, 1974 October 7-16; 1112; 1 box (Box 832)
      - Senator Mansfield, 1974 October 10; 1472; 5 minutes (Box 832)
      - Thousands at Sioux Falls College, 1974 October 14; 1123; 1 box (Box 832)
      - David Brinkley, NBC TV, 1974 October 16; 1332; 1 box (Box 832)
      - Debate-1974 Campaign, 1974 October 20; 1111; 1 box (Box 832)
      - KSF 4 Debate, 1974 October 20; 1521; 1 box (Box 832)
      - McGovern KISD Interview, 1974 October 21; 380; 1 box (Box 832)
      - CBS TV, 1974 October 22; 1333; 1 box (Box 832)
      - Reel S 7 Spots, 1974 October 29; 903; 60 seconds (Box 832)
      - McGovern, 1974 December 2; portion of 1 box (Box 832)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1427, 1430, 1431.
      - Livestock, Medicare, Railroad, 1974 December 2; 1435; 1 box (Box 832)
      - McGovern, 1974 December 2; portion of 1 box (Box 832)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1437, 1487, 1489, 1491, 1495, 1508-1520.
      - Kansas City/Hunger Conference and Issues and Answers, 1974 December 8; 578; 1 box (Box 832)
      - ABC Perspective Radio, 1974 December 14-15; 1323; 1 box (Box 832)
      - McGovern, 1974 December 17; portion of 1 box (Box 832)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1425, 1426, 1428, 1429, 1433, 1434, 1438, 1488, 1490, 1492-1494, 1496-1507.
      - Economics Conference, Press Conference, 1974 December 17; 1436; 1 box (Box 832)
      - No. 581 Senator McGovern; 2 spots; LBC; DUB, 1975 February 3; 39; 2-inch 1 box (Box 832)
      - #1, #2, 1975 February 3; 1473; 2 minutes 20 seconds; 2 minutes 15 seconds (Box 833)
      - Middle East/Indochina, 1975 March 19; 1471; 1 box (Box 833)
      - #1-5, 1975 April 25; 980; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Tomorrow and Today, 1975 May 9-12; 585; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Roundtable and McGovern in Cuba, 1975 May 12; 575; 1 box (Box 833)
      - McGovern-Castro TV, Food Stamps, 1975 June 16; 573; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Senator McGovern/Senator Abrough, 1975 June 17; 378; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Senator Edmund Muskie, 1975 June 23; 571; 1 box (Box 833)
      - National Press Club, Lou Harris, 1975 June 26; 1 box (Box 833)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 379, 389.
      - ABC Radio Perspective, 1975 June 27; 574; 1 box (Box 833)
      - TV, 1975 June 30; 363; 1 box (Box 833)
      - 1975 July 2, 570; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Shirley MacLaine on McGovern, 1975 July 19; 558; 1 box (Box 833)
      - McGovern on Castro, 1975 July 30; 598; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Cuba, 1975 August 21; 572; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Agronsky-Evening Edition, 1975 September 26; 594; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Food Stamps, 1975 October 7; 593; 1 box (Box 833)
      - South Dakota, 1975 October 24; 576; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Callaway Interview, 1975 November 23-24; 595; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Today and Washington Week in Review, 1975 November 26-28; 557; 1 box (Box 833)
      - California State University, 1976; 390; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Remarks at the American Club, Islamabad, Pakistan, 1976 January 5; 374; 1 box (Box 833)
      - McGovern Interviews in Islamabad, Pakistan, 1976 January 6; 386; 1 box (Box 833)
      - McGovern Interview at Lahore Airport, 1976 January 6; 604; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Tomorrow with Tom Snyder, 1976 January 29; 561; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Agronsky-Evening Edition, 1976 June 9; 563; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Issues and Answers, 1976 July 11; 373; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Democratic Convention Address, 1976 July 13; 562; 1 box (Box 833)
      - Alcoholics Anonymous, 1977 February 10; 41; 30 minutes 2-inch color) (Box 833)
      - Senator McGovern P.S.A., 1977 March 11; 38; 42 seconds 2-inch (Box 833)
      - #05, Senator McGovern, 1977 April 22; 671; 13 minutes 50 seconds U-Matic KCS-20 master) (Box 833)
      - #32 Senator McGovern, 1977 April 28; 658; 13 minutes 50 seconds UCA-60 (Box 833)
      - #32 Senator McGovern, 1977 April 28; 669; 13 minutes 50 seconds U-Matic KCS-20 (Box 833)
      - Spots #1-4, 1977 April 28; 1115; 13 minutes 50 seconds (Box 834)
      - #8, Master #1, 1977 May 5; 979; 1 box (Box 834)
      - Senator McGovern #218, 1977 July 25; 664; 21 minutes 8 seconds Memorex U-Matic UCA-30 (Box 834)
      - #303 Senator McGovern, 1977 September 22; 1984 February 22; 659; 7 minutes 21 seconds U-Matic UCA 30 (Box 834)
      - #303 Senator McGovern, 1977 September 22; 670; 7 minutes 21 seconds U-Matic KCS 20 (Box 834)
      - NBC TV Today, 1978 January 9; 607; 1 box (Box 834)
      - Florida Forum, 1978 April 16; 1615; 1 box (Box 834)
      - 20/20 Show: Agent Change, 1978 July 25; 665; Ampex KCA-60 1 box (Box 834)
      - McGovern on Cambodia, 1978 August 23; 629; UCA-20 1 box (Box 834)
      - McGovern Railroads, 1978 November 9; 630; U-Matic KC-30 1 box (Box 834)
      - Speech-South Africa, 1978 December 7; 1446; 1 box (Box 834)
      - TV Interview, 1979 January 29; 1618; 1 box (Box 834)
      - Speech to National Television Co-Op Asociation, 1979 February 21; 1628; 1 box (Box 834)
      - McGovern-Africa, 1979 February 25; 657; 30 minutes U-Matic KCA-60 (Box 834)
      - TV Interview #2, 1979 March 1; 1602; 1 box (Box 834)
      - Rock Island Press Conference, 1979 March 17; 1609; 1 box (Box 834)
      - Red Alert, 1979 April 3; 620; 30 minutes Betamax (Box 834)
      - TV Interview Show #3, 1979 April 10; 1600; 1 box (Box 834)
      - TV Interview #4, 1979 May 10; 1138; 1 box (Box 834)
      - TV Interview #5, 1979 June 14; 1619; 1 box (Box 834)
      - KABY-KSFY Interview, 1979 June 28; 1607; 1 box (Box 834)
      - KOTA-KYON Interview, 1979 July 18; 1605; 1 box (Box 834)
      - Senator McGovern #740, 1979 July 30; 615; 35 seconds Ampex KCA-20 (Box 834)
      - TV Interview KEVN-KELO, 1979 August 1; 1601; 1 box (Box 834)
      - Kenkloro News Conference, Rapid City, 1979 August 9; 1137; 1 box (Box 835)
      - McGovern-Janklow TV Debate, 1979 August 23; 653; U-Matic KCA-60 1 box (Box 835)
      - McGovern-Janklow Debate, 1979 August 23; 1119; 1 box (Box 835)
      - Visit to Winthrop High School, 1979 October 19; 549; 60 minutes Ampex KCA-60 (Box 835)
      - TV Interview, 1979 October 24; 1134; 1 box (Box 835)
      - Here's Info, NFO Radio: Price of Wheat, 1979 November; 1610; 1 box (Box 835)
      - Senator McGovern #005, 1979 November 7; 661; 14 minutes 13 seconds U-Matic KCS-20 (Box 835)
      - Face the Nation, CBS TV, 1979 November 11; 1620; 1 box (Box 835)
      - TV Show #10, 1979 November 27; 1599; 1 box (Box 835)
  - Subseries 5D, 1980-1984; 3.5 linear feet 4 boxes
    This subseries documents McGovern's unsuccessful 1980 Senate reelection campaign as well as his unsuccessful 1984 bid for the Democratic presidential nomination.
    Subseries 5D is arranged chronologically.
    - ECN, 1980; 16mm 2 boxes (Box 836, Box 837)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 434, 435.
    - McGovern vs. Robin S. Johnson: Should Wheat Producing Nations Jointly Raise Prices?, 1980; 1133; 1 box (Box 838)
    - Senator McGovern, 1980 January 1; 672; 11 minutes 21 seconds U-Matic KCS-20 (Box 838)
    - Daley, 1980 January 24; 915; 1 box (Box 838)
    - NN A/C McGovern, 1980 January 26; 667; U-Matic KCS-20 1 box (Box 838)
    - #209 Senator McGovern for President, 1980 January 29; 660; 11 minutes 21 seconds Ampex BCA-30 (Box 838)
    - #209 Senator McGovern, 1980 January 29; 662; 11 minutes 21 seconds U-Matic KCS-20 (Box 838)
    - TV Interview #11, 1980 January 29; 1136; 1 box (Box 838)
    - The Music Man, 1980 April 14; U-Matic KCA-60 portion of 1 box (Box 838)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 655, 666.
    - Abdnor, 1980 May; 621; 5 minutes Betamax (Box 838)
    - McGovern, 1980 May 9; 681; 5 minutes (Box 838)
    - Salt II, 1980 August 4; 1109; 1 box (Box 838)
    - McGovern-Spots #3, 1980 September 9; 1145; 16mm 1 box (Box 838)
    - Jackson Press Conference, 1980 October 3; 1117; 1 box (Box 838)
    - McGovern Speech in Plankington, South Dakota, 1980 October 9; portion of 1 box (Box 838)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 1604, 1606.
    - Mondale, Florida University Convention, 1980 October 13; 1108; 1 box (Box 838)
    - McGovern Press Conference, 1980 October 23; 1118; 1 box (Box 838)
    - McGovern and Scoop Jackson, Rapid City Press Conference, 1980 October 31; 1106; 2 minutes (Box 838)
    - McGovern Campaign Video, 1980 November 2-3; 611; 30 minutes U-Matic KCA-30 (Box 838)
    - McGovern Concession Speech, 1980 November 4; 1120; 1 box (Box 838)
    - George McGovern, San Jose, CA Headliners, 1983 November 6; 612; 30 minutes color) (Box 838)
    - Askew-McGovern, 1983 December 2; 623; MBU 18s 1 box (Box 838)
    - Ken Swope Demo, 1984; 553; 15 minutes (Box 838)
    - Ken Swope, 1984; 613; 15 minutes (Box 838)
    - NN A/C McGovern, 1984 January 26; 656; U-Matic KCA-60 1 box (Box 838)
    - Making Sense McGovern for President, 1984 February 10; 619; 21 minutes Betamax (Box 839)
    - George McGovern for President Issues, 1984 February 11; 19; 3/4-inch edit master) 1 box (Box 839)
    - McGovern for President, Issues, 1984 February 13; Ampex BCA-30 1 box (Box 839)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 548, 618.
    - George McGovern Political, 1984 February 14; 628; 30 seconds UCA-20s (Box 839)
    - McGovern Interview with Bill Curtis and McGovern and Mrs. McGovern with Diane Sawyer, 1984 February 17; 1983 December 12; 627; U-Matic KCS-20 1 box (Box 839)
    - McGovern for President Central America, 1984 February 26; 663; Ampex BCA-30 1 box (Box 839)
  - Subseries 5E: Undated Material, 1967-1968; 29 linear feet 30 boxes
    This subseries contains materials of all formats that lack date information. Titles consisting of a number assigned by McGovern's office have been retained, though their meaning remains unclear.
    Subseries 5E is arranged alphabetically. Titles consisting of a number only are filed at the end of the subseries.
    - ABC News McGovern, undated; 626; U-Matic KCS-20 1 box (Box 839)
    - Aberdeen: People of Redfield, Sewer Required, Nice Little Curve, undated; 588; 1 box (Box 839)
    - Abrams, Bob Testimonial Dinner, New York City, undated; 1582; 1 box (Box 839)
    - Acceptance Speech, undated; 504; 16mm 1 box (Box 839)
    - Actualities, New Mexico, undated; 131; 1 box (Box 839)
    - Actualities, Massachusetts, undated; 144; master) 1 box (Box 839)
    - Actualities, Wisconsin, undated; 139; master) 1 box (Box 839)
    - Actualities, No. 1, undated; 163; master) 1 box (Box 839)
    - A Dakota Story, undated; 16mm portion of 1 box (Box 840)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 3, 10, 471.
    - After Vietnam and Peace Economies, undated; 1056; 1 box (Box 840)
    - Amendment to End the War, undated; 16mm portion of 1 box (Box 840)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 437, 451.
    - Amendment to End the War, undated; 530; 60 seconds 16mm color) (Box 840)
    - Amendment to End the War, 2 spots, undated; 1245; 60 seconds (Box 840)
    - Amendment to End the War CBS Interview, undated; 468; 16mm 1 box (Box 841)
    - Amendment to End the War: Change Our Minds, undated; 1682; 16mm 1 box (Box 842)
    - Amendment to End the War: Inflation, undated; 182; 16mm 1 box (Box 842)
    - Amendment to End the War: Senators, undated; 1685; 16mm 1 box (Box 842)
    - Amendment to End the War: 12 Year Old, undated; 1684; 2 reels 16mm (Box 842)
    - Amendment to End the War: 39, undated; 2; 16mm 1 box (Box 842)
    - Andy Williams Battle Hymn, undated; 440; 16mm 1 box (Box 842)
    - Angola 2, undated; 1459; 1 box (Box 842)
    - Bank Stabilization, Yankton, undated; 589; 1 box (Box 842)
    - Mr. Bertsch, undated; 498; 1 box (Box 842)
    - Black Radio Interview, undated; 1207; 1 box (Box 842)
    - Bob K Recording, undated; 1409; 1 box (Box 842)
    - Bountiful Harvest, undated; 456; 16mm 1 box (Box 842)
    - Brinkley Journal Peru/School Lunch J. Syminton, undated; 81; 16mm 1 box (Box 842)
    - Burnham, undated; 30 seconds 16mm (Box 842)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 481, 491, 538.
    - Businessmen, #7, undated; 5 minutes 16mm color) (Box 842)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 206, 509, 510, 517, 693, 708, 710.
    - Businessmen, #7, undated; 654; U-Matic KCA-60 1 box (Box 842)
    - Byrd, undated; 16mm 1/4 inch on reel core portion of 1 box (Box 843)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 103, 104.
    - Byrd, undated; 114; 16mm 2 3/4-inch on reel core 1 box (Box 843)
    - California #1, May 29 -June 2, no year; 1374; master) 1 box (Box 843)
    - California #2, undated; 129; 1 box (Box 843)
    - California, May 31 no year; 138; 1 box (Box 843)
    - California Primary, Stockton, undated; 140; 1 box (Box 843)
    - California Primary, Reaction, undated; 1587; 1 box (Box 843)
    - California Rallies, Corvina and Fairfax, Los Angeles- Israel, undated; 744; 1 box (Box 843)
    - California, Southern: Primary, undated; 882; 1 box (Box 843)
    - California Rally, Fairfax High School, September 25 no year; 273; 1 box (Box 843)
    - California: San Diego, October 14 no year; 1390; 1 box (Box 843)
    - Campus Registration, undated; 1573; 1 box (Box 843)
    - Castro Interview, undated; 1443; 1 box (Box 843)
    - Castro/Vietnam, undated; 1451; 1 box (Box 843)
    - CBS NY, undated; 59; 2-inch 1 box (Box 843)
    - Classroom, undated; 520; 16mm 1 box (Box 843)
    - Come Home America, undated; 1281; 1 box (Box 843)
    - Communities on Oneonta Station WDOS by Stan Weisberger, undated; 173; 1 box (Box 843)
    - Constituents, undated; 20 seconds 16mm b/w (Box 843)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 183, 478, 537, 718, 720.
    - Convers-Brown, Cleveland Press Conference, undated; 1565; 1 box (Box 843)
    - Corn, undated; 99; 16mm 1 box (Box 843)
    - Corn Palace, undated; 16mm portion of 1 box (Box 843)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 635, 640.
    - Corn Palace Farm, undated; 684; 1 box (Box 843)
    - Corn Palace Rear, undated; 110; 16mm 1 box (Box 843)
    - Corn Palace R.L. Pictures, undated; 406; 16mm 1 box (Box 844)
    - CTV News, undated; 1591; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Cuba, McGovern in, undated; 652; 1 hour 2 minutes 45 seconds U-Matic KC-60 (Box 844)
    - Cuba-McGovern Departure, undated; 93; 16mm 1 box (Box 844)
    - Cuban Embargo Recording, undated; 1449; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Dallas/Rocklord, undated; 1293; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Darrow Film, undated; 501; 16mm 1 box (Box 844)
    - Darrow, Wayne Wheat Interview, KXAB-TV, undated; 13 minutes 15 Seconds 16mm (Box 844)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 1728, 1771.
    - Democratic Radio Spots, undated; 1253; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Denholm, undated; 1302; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Discussion with South Dakota's Girl's Nation Delegates, undated; 342; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Eleanor McGovern #1-2, undated; portion of 1 box (Box 844)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 1603, 1608.
    - Eleanor McGovern, undated; 116; 16mm 1 box (Box 844)
    - Eleanor McGovern and Pierre Salinger, undated; 1178; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Eleanor McGovern Interview in the Bronx, undated; 1064; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Election '72, undated; 395; 3/4-inch 1 box (Box 844)
    - The Election and Survival Interview, undated; 911; 1 box (Box 844)
    - ENO of Farm, undated; 94; 16mm 1 box (Box 844)
    - Ensign O'Toms (?) Sabotage, undated; 459; 16mm 1 box (Box 885)
    - Eugenia Hartis, KELO-TV, Sioux Falls, South Dakota, undated; 631; U-Matic UCA-30 1 box (Box 844)
    - Evening Banquet, undated; 1626; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Face the Nation, undated; 750; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Face the Nation, Humphrey-McGovern Special, undated; 1351; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Face the Nation, O'Hara, July 9 no year; 1367; 1 box (Box 844)
    - Farm, undated; 909; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Farm Fest, Minnesota, undated; 255; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Firing Line Series: SALT talks Part I and Part II, undated; 550; U-Matic KCA-60 1 box (Box 845)
    - Firing Line #341, Salt Talks: Part II, undated; 624; U-Matic KCA-60 1 box (Box 845)
    - Firing Line #1326 Buckley-McGovern Debate Resolved: That President Reagan Should Be Reelected in 1984, Parts 1 and 2, undated; 651; UCA-60 1 box (Box 845)
    - First McGovern Press Conference, undated; 1455; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Florida Documentary, undated; 79; 16mm 1 box (Box 845)
    - Floyd Interview, Geneva, Switzerland, undated; 449; 16mm answer print) 1 box (Box 845)
    - Food, undated; 644; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Friends of Oahe TV Show, undated; 1589; 30 minutes (Box 845)
    - Frontier of Trade, undated; 190; 16mm 1 box (Box 845)
    - Good Democrats, One and All, undated; 1284; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Genderen, Bob van, undated; 1102; 1 box (Box 845)
    - German, George and Sharon Kreber, undated; 1421; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Grain Elevator, undated; 910; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Graves and Crow, undated; 500; 16mm 1 box (Box 845)
    - GUC, undated; 229; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Harris, Fred, undated; portion of 1 box (Box 845)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 1578, 1592.
    - Hartke, undated; 16mm portion of 1 box (Box 845)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 523, 524.
    - Homestead Agrarian Reform, May 5 no year; 1461; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Humphrey Spots, undated; portion of 1 box (Box 845)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 1251, 1252.
    - Humphrey, undated; 1419; 1 box (Box 845)
    - Humphrey, undated; 458; 16mm 1 box (Box 845)
    - Humphrey, undated; 486; 60 seconds 16mm (Box 845)
    - Hubert H. Humphrey Island of Lost Souls, undated; 473; 16mm 1 box (Box 846)
      Contains 2 reels
    - Humphrey/McGovern, Waldorf-Astoria, New York City, October 20 no year; 1634; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Humphrey-Minneapolis; McGovern on Labor, Washington, August 24-25 no year; 1636; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Humphrey on Issues and Answers, undated; 1403; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Humphrey/Wheat Referendum, undated; 16mm portion of 1 box (Box 847)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 7, 438, 446.
    - Hunger, undated; 252; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Hunger, undated; 60 seconds 16mm (Box 847)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 489, 715.
    - Illinois-Pennsylvania, October 11 no year; 1393; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Investigation of Police Protection for Rosebud-Sioux Indians, undated; 1153; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Irrigation, undated; 113; 16mm 1 box (Box 847)
    - Keene State, undated; 1290; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kefauver, undated; 949; 16mm negative print) 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy, KXAB-TV, undated; 528; 16mm 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy For President, Schools-Primary, 7-35-IM, undated; 1475; 16mm 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy For President-Do Better, undated; 189; 16mm 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy Quote for Headquarters Radio News Department, undated; 168; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy, Robert Spot Ads, undated; 1249; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy, Robert Spot Ads, undated; 1562; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy, Robert #4, undated; 452; 16mm 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy, Robert Special, undated; 256; 1 box (Box 847)
    - Kennedy, Robert versus Mitchell, undated; 334; 1 box (Box 847)